Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 20th Century Architecture (Box 41)
  - Britain (Box 43)
    - Places (Box 43)
      - Cambridge [Slide box 259] (Box 44)
        - History Faculty (Box 44)
        - University Library (Box 44)
      - Canterbury (Box 44)
      - Cardiff (Box 44)
      - Cardiganshire, Wales (Box 44)
      - Castle Morton (Box 44)
      - Chatsworth (Box 44)
      - Cheadle (Box 44)
      - Cheshire (Box 44)
      - Chiswick (Box 44)
      - Chorley Wood (Box 44)
      - Chussex (Box 44)
      - Clevedon (Box 44)
      - Clifton (Box 44)
      - Clumber Park, Nots. (Box 44)
      - Coalpit Heath (Box 44)
      - Colwall (Box 44)
      - Combe Down (Box 44)
      - Compton (Box 44)
      - Cork [Slide box 260] (Box 44)
      - Coventry (Box 44)
      - Cragside (Box 44)
      - Cumbernauld (Box 44)
      - Darlington (Box 44)
      - Deanery Garden (Box 44)
      - Deepdene (Box 44)
      - Devonport (Box 44)
      - Dodington (Box 44)
      - Dublin (Box 44)
      - Ealing (Box 44)
      - East Grinstead (Box 44)
      - East Knoyle (Box 44)
      - Eastnor (Box 44)
      - Edensor (Box 44)
      - Edinburgh (Box 44)
      - Edgham, Surrey (Box 44)
      - Finsbury (Box 44)
      - Folly Farm (Box 44)
      - Fonthill Abbey [Slide box 261] (Box 44)
      - Frensham (Box 44)
      - Frinton-on-Sea (Box 44)
      - Glasgow (Box 44)
        - Churches (Box 44)
        - Restaurants (Box 44)
          - Willow Tea Rooms (Box 44)
      - Schools (Box 44)
        - School of Art [Slide boxes 261-262] (Box 44)
      - Grange Park [Slide box 262] (Box 44)
      - Great Dixter (Box 44)
      - Greyfriars (near Guildford) (Box 44)
      - Grey Walls (Box 44)
      - Groombridge (Box 44)
      - Guildford (Box 44)
      - Halland (Box 44)
      - Halnaker Park, Sussex (Box 44)
      - Halwill (Box 44)
      - Hamels (Box 44)
      - Hampstead Garden Suburb (Box 44)
        - S. Jude's (Box 44)
      - Harlow New Town (Box 44)
      - Harrow Weald (Box 44)
      - Haslemere, Surrey [Slide boxes 262-263] (Box 44)
      - Heathcote [Slide box 263] (Box 44)
      - Helensburgh (Box 44)
      - Hemel Hempstead, New Town (Box 44)
      - Hestercombe (Box 44)
      - Homewood (Box 44)
      - Hull (Box 44)
      - Hunstanton (Box 44)
      - Impington (Box 44)
      - Ipswich (Box 44)
      - Isle of Wight (Box 44)
      - Kelmscott Manor, Oxfordshire (Box 44)
      - Kew (Box 44)
      - Kilcreggan (Box 44)
      - Killymoon Castle (Box 44)
      - Kilmacolm (Box 44)
      - Kinmel Park [Slide box 264] (Box 44)
      - Knotty Green (Box 44)
      - Laxton Hall (Box 44)
      - Leeds (Box 44)
      - Leicester (Box 44)
      - Letchworth Gardens (Box 44)
      - Letton Hall (Box 44)
      - Limerick (Box 44)
      - Little Thakeham (Box 44)
      - Liverpool (Box 44)
        - Churches [Slide boxes 264-265] (Box 44–45)
        - Office Buildings [Slide box 265] (Box 45)
      - London (Box 45)
        - Plans (Box 45)
        - Planning (Box 45)
        - General Views (Box 45)
          - Streets (Box 45)
          - Chelsea (Box 45)
        - Banks (Box 45)
          - Bank of England [Slide boxes 265-266] (Box 45)
        - Cemeteries [Slide box 266] (Box 45)
        - Churches (Box 45)
          - All Saint's Margaret Street (Box 45)
          - All Soul's Church (Box 45)
          - Oratory (Box 45)
          - S. Martin's (Box 45)
          - Westminster Cathedral (Box 45)
        - Clubs (Box 45)
        - Exhibitions (Box 45)
          - Crystal Palace (Box 45)
            - Exterior [Slide boxes 266-267] (Box 45)
            - Interior [Slide box 267] (Box 45)
          - Festival of Britain, 1951 (Box 45)
        - Government Buildings (Box 45)
          - Law Courts [Slide boxes 267-268] (Box 45)
          - Parliament [Slide box 268] (Box 45)
          - U.S. Embassy (Box 45)
        - Hospitals (Box 45)
        - House- Apartments (Box 45)
        - House-Residential (Box 45)
          - Annesley Lodge (Box 45)
          - Cadogan Gardens #25 (Box 45)
          - Cheyne Walk Houses (Box 45)
          - Freud's House (Box 45)
          - Hans Road #14-16 (Box 45)
          - Lowther Lodge (Box 45)
          - John Nash Houses (Box 45)
          - Melbury Road, #31 (Box 45)
          - Queen's Gate Houses (Box 45)
          - Soane House and Museum (Box 45)
          - Swan House, Chelsea (Box 45)
          - Three Gables (Box 45)
        - Housing (Box 45)
          - Ham Common Housing (Box 45)
          - Roehampton Apartments (Box 45)
        - Libraries (Box 45)
        - Monuments [Slide boxes 269-270] (Box 45)
        - Museums [Slide box 270] (Box 45)
          - British Museum (Box 45)
          - Dulwich Gallery (Box 45)
          - Fine Art Society (Box 45)
          - Grosvenor Gallery (Box 45)
          - Marlborough House (Box 45)
          - National Gallery (Box 45)
            - Sainsbury Wing Competition (Box 45)
            - Sainbury Wing (Venturi) [Slide box 271] (Box 46)
            - Natural History Museum (Box 46)
            - Royal Academy (Box 46)
            - Saatchi Collection (Box 46)
            - Tate Gallery (Box 46)
              - Clore Gallery (Stirling) (Box 46)
            - Tate Modern (Box 46)
            - Victoria and Albert Museum (Box 46)
        - Office Buildings [Slide boxes 271-272] (Box 46)
          - Brittanic House [Slide box 272] (Box 46)
          - Economist Buildings (Box 46)
          - Lloyd's of London (Box 46)
        - Palaces (Box 46)
        - Parks (Box 46)
          - Regent's Park (Box 46)
          - Cumberland Terrace [Slide boxes 272-273] (Box 46)
        - Schools [Slide box 273] (Box 46)
        - Squares (Box 46)
        - Stations (Box 46)
        - St. Pancras (Box 46)
        - Stores (Box 46)
        - Theaters (Box 46)
        - Warehouses (Box 46)
        - Zoos (Box 46)
      - Manchester [Slide boxes 273-274] (Box 46)
      - Marshcourt [Slide box 274] (Box 46)
      - Melchet Park (Box 46)
      - Mentmore (Box 46)
      - Merrist Wood (Box 46)
      - Middlefield (Box 46)
      - Middleton Park (Box 46)
      - Milton Ernest (Box 46)
      - Moor Crag (Box 46)
      - Munstead Wood (Box 46)
      - Nashdom (Box 46)
      - New Lanark, Scotland (Box 46)
      - New Place (Box 46)
      - Nitshill (Box 46)
      - Norney Grange (Box 46)
      - Northampton [Slide box 275] (Box 46)
      - Norwich (Box 46)
      - Nottingham (Box 46)
      - Orpington (Box 46)
      - Orchards (Box 46)
      - Overstrand, Norfolk (Box 46)
      - Oxford (Box 46)
        - Ashmolean Museum (Box 46)
        - Keble College (Box 46)
        - Queen's College (Box 46)
        - University Museum [Slide boxes 275-276] (Box 46)
      - Papillon Hall [Slide box 276] (Box 46)
      - The Pastures (Box 46)
      - Penzance, Cornwall (Box 46)
      - Phillips House (Box 46)
      - Plumpton Place (Box 46)
      - Polesden Lacey (Box 46)
      - Port Sunlight (Box 46)
      - Preston (Box 46)
      - Rampisham (Box 46)
      - Ramsgate (Box 46)
      - Richmond (Box 46)
      - Rockingham (Box 46)
      - Rugby (Box 46)
      - Runcorn New Town (Box 46)
      - St. Andrews (Fife, Scotland) (Box 46)
      - S. Mawgan (Box 46)
      - Salisbury (Box 46)
      - The Salutation (Box 46)
      - Sandridge Park (Box 46)
      - Saxlingham (Box 46)
      - Scarisbrick Hall (Box 46)
      - Sezincote (Box 46)
      - Sheffield [Slide boxes 276-277] (Box 46–47)
      - Solihull [Slide box 277] (Box 47)
      - Southborough Place (Box 47)
      - Stevenage (Box 47)
      - Stowe (Box 47)
      - Stratford-on-Avon (Box 47)
      - Studland (Box 47)
      - Swindon (Box 47)
      - Tendring Hall (Box 47)
      - Tigbourne Court (Box 47)
      - Upton M agma (Box 47)
      - Watford (Box 47)
      - Welwyn Garden City (Box 47)
      - West Hartlepool (Box 47)
      - Whitwood (Box 47)
      - Wightwick Manor (Box 47)
      - Willington, Cheshire (Box 47)
      - Wimpole Hall (Box 47)
      - Winchester (Box 47)
      - Windsor (Box 47)
      - Witley Court (Box 47)
      - York (Box 47)
  - Bulgaria [Slide box 278] (Box 47)
    - Various (Box 47)
  - Czechoslovakia (Box 47)
    - Bohdanec (Box 47)
    - Brno (Box 47)
    - Pilsen (Box 47)
    - Prague (Box 47)
      - Muller House (Box 47)
  - Denmark (Box 47)
    - Lund, Nils-Ole (Box 47)
    - Aarlus [Slide boxes 278-279] (Box 47)
    - Copenhagen [Slide box 279] (Box 47)
      - Churches (Box 47)
      - Government Buildings (Box 47)
      - Hospitals (Box 47)
      - Houses- Apartments (Box 47)
      - Museums (Box 47)
      - Parks (Box 47)
      - Schools (Box 47)
      - Squares (Box 47)
  - Egypt (Box 47)
    - Fathy, Hassan (Box 47)
    - Cairo (Box 47)
    - Dahshur (Box 47)
    - El Gouna (Box 47)
    - Kharga Oasis (Box 47)
    - New Gourna (Box 47)
  - Finland [Slide box 280] (Box 47)
    - Aalto, Alvar (Box 47)
    - Helsinki (Box 47)
    - Imatra (Box 47)
    - Jyvaskyla (Box 47)
    - Noormarkku (Box 47)
    - Otaniemi (Box 47)
    - Paimion (Box 47)
    - Rovaniemi (Box 47)
    - Saynatsalo [Slide boxes 280-281] (Box 47)
    - Seinajoki [Slide box 281] (Box 47)
    - Sunila (Box 47)
    - Tampere (Box 47)
    - Turku (Box 47)
    - Viipuri (Box 47)
  - France (Box 47)
    - General (Box 47)
      - French Academy (Box 47)
    - Architects (Box 47)
      - Boitte, F.P. (Box 47)
      - Boileau, L-H (Box 47)
      - Bonnier, Louis (Box 47)
      - Borie, Henri-Jules (Box 47)
      - Fourier, Charles (Box 47)
      - Friedman, Yona [Slide boxes 281-282] (Box 47)
      - Garnier, Tony [Slide box 282] (Box 47)
      - Labrouste, Henri (Box 47)
      - Labrouste, Theodore (Box 47)
      - Le Corbusier (Box 47)
        - Algiers Project (Box 47)
        - Latin American Cities (Box 47)
        - Maniere de Penser l'Urbanisme (Box 47)
        - City for 3 Million (Box 47)
        - "Voisin" Plan for Paris (Box 47)
        - Le Modulor [Slide box 283] (Box 48)
        - Travel Sketches (Box 48)
        - Vers Une Architecture (Box 48)
      - Lequeu, J.J. (Box 48)
        - Architecture Civile (Box 48)
        - Figures et Architecture (Box 48)
        - Percier and Fontaine [Slide boxes 283-284] (Box 48)
        - Perriand, Charlotte [Slide box 284] (Box 48)
        - Viollet-le-Duc (Box 48)
    - Cities (Box 48)
      - Albert (Box 48)
      - Angers (Box 48)
      - Asnieres (Box 48)
      - Assy (Box 48)
      - Auteuil (Box 48)
      - Bar-le-Duc (Box 48)
      - Bazoches-sur-Guyonne (Box 48)
      - Bordeaux (Box 48)
      - Castellar (Box 48)
      - Cergy Pontoise [Slide box 285] (Box 48)
      - Dax (Box 48)
      - Dieppe (Box 48)
      - Disneyland Paris (Box 48)
      - Epinay-sur-Seine (Box 48)
      - Etretat (Box 48)
      - Eveux-sur-Arbresle (Box 48)
      - Ferrieres (Box 48)
      - Garches [Slide boxes 285-286] (Box 48)
      - Gisors [Slide box 286] (Box 48)
      - Grigny (Box 48)
      - Guise (Box 48)
      - Honfleur (Box 48)
      - Hermanville-sur-Mer (Box 48)
      - Hyeres (Box 48)
      - Kembs-Niffer (Box 48)
      - Le Havre (Box 48)
      - Le Raincy (Box 48)
      - Le Vesinet (Box 48)
      - Lille (Box 48)
      - Lyon (Box 48)
      - Marne-la-Vallee [Slide boxes 286-287] (Box 48)
      - Marseilles [Slide box 287] (Box 48)
        - Cultural Center (Box 48)
        - Unite d'Habitation (Box 48)
      - Montpellier (Box 48)
      - Mulhouse (Box 48)
      - Nancy (Box 48)
      - Narbonne (Box 48)
      - Neuilly (Box 48)
      - Nimes (Box 48)
      - Orcival [Slide box 288] (Box 48)
      - Orly (Box 48)
      - Parc Beausejour (Box 48)
      - Paris (Box 48)
        - American Center (Box 48)
        - Plans (Box 48)
          - Arrondissement Maps (Box 48)
        - Planning [Slide boxes 288-289] (Box 48–49)
        - General Views [Slide box 289] (Box 49)
          - Air View (Box 49)
          - Hoffbauer Views (Box 49)
          - Night Views (Box 49)
          - Outdoor Pavilions (Box 49)
          - Seine [Slide boxes 289-290] (Box 49)
          - Streets [Slide box 290] (Box 49)
          - Suburbs (Box 49)
        - Arches (Box 49)
          - Arc du Carousel (Box 49)
          - Arc de Triomphe (Box 49)
        - Banks (Box 49)
        - Baths (Box 49)
        - Bridges (Box 49)
        - Canals (Box 49)
        - Cemeteries (Box 49)
        - Churches [Slide boxes 290-291] (Box 49)
          - La Madeleine [Slide boxes 291] (Box 49)
          - Sacre-Coeur de Montmartre (Box 49)
          - S. Jean de Montmartre (Box 49)
          - S. Pierre de Montmartre (Box 49)
        - Circuses (Box 49)
        - Expositions (Box 49)
          - Exposition 1855 (Box 49)
          - Exposition 1867 (Box 49)
          - Exposition 1878 (Box 49)
          - International Exposition 1889 [Slide boxes 291-292] (Box 49)
            - Eiffel Tower [Slide box 292] (Box 49)
            - Hall (Galerie) of Machines (Box 49)
          - Exposition Universelle, 1900 (Box 49)
            - Austrian Pavilion (Box 49)
            - Pavilion l'Esprit Nouveau [Slide boxes 292-293] (Box 49)
            - Russian Pavilion [Slide box 293] (Box 49)
            - Space City (Box 49)
          - Societe Artistes Decorateurs, Salon 1930 (Box 49)
          - Colonial Exposition, 1931 (Box 49)
          - International Exposition, 1937 (Box 49)
            - Aeronautical Pavilion (Box 49)
            - German Pavilion (Box 49)
            - Railroad Pavilion (Box 49)
            - Spanish Pavilion (Box 49)
            - Temps Nouveau Pavilion [Slide box 294] (Box 49)
        - Gates (Box 49)
        - Garages (Box 49)
        - Government Buildings (Box 49)
          - UNESCO Building (Box 49)
        - Hospitals (Box 49)
        - Hotels (Box 49)
        - Houses-Residential (Box 49)
          - Hotel Guimard (Box 49)
          - Maison de Verre (Box 49)
          - Mallet-Stevens Houses (Box 49)
          - Ozenfant House (Box 49)
          - Tzara (Box 49)
          - Weekend (Box 49)
          - Villa dall'Ava [Slide box 295] (Box 50)
        - Houses-Apartments (Box 50)
          - Badovici Apartment (Box 50)
          - Beistegui (Box 50)
          - C. Beranger (Box 50)
          - 25 Rue Franklin (Box 50)
          - Rue Raynourd Apartments (Box 50)
        - Housing (Box 50)
          - Cite Napoleon (Box 50)
          - Foundation Rothschild (Box 50)
          - Maison des Ouvriers (Box 50)
        - Libraries (Box 50)
          - Bibliotheque Nationale (Box 50)
          - Bibliotheque S. Genevieve [Slide boxes 295-296] (Box 50)
        - Markets [Slide box 296] (Box 50)
          - Central Market (Les Halles) (Box 50)
        - Mosques (Box 50)
        - Museums (Box 50)
          - Arts Africains et Oceaniens (Box 50)
          - Louvre (Box 50)
            - Historical Views (Box 50)
            - Exterior (Box 50)
              - Entrance Pyramid (Box 50)
              - Seine (South) Sidec (Box 50)
              - Rue de Rivoli (North) Side (Box 50)
          - Monuments Francais [Slide box 297] (Box 50)
          - Musee d'Orsay (Box 50)
          - Pompidou Center (Box 50)
        - Office Buildings (Box 50)
          - Salvation Army Headquarters (Box 50)
        - Parks (Box 50)
          - Bois de Boulogne (Box 50)
          - Buttes-Chaumont (Box 50)
          - Vicennes (Box 50)
          - Villette (Box 50)
        - Prisons (Box 50)
        - Restaurants [Slide boxes 297-298] (Box 50)
        - Schools [Slide box 298] (Box 50)
          - Arab World Institute (Box 50)
          - University City (Box 50)
            - Foreign Pavilion (Box 50)
            - Swiss Pavilion (Box 50)
              - Exterior (Box 50)
              - Interior (Box 50)
        - Squares (Box 50)
          - Place de la Concorde (Box 50)
        - Stations (Box 50)
          - Gare de l'Est [Slide box 299] (Box 50)
          - Gare S. Lazare (Box 50)
          - Metro Stations (Box 50)
        - Stores (Box 50)
          - Bon Marche (Box 50)
          - Galerie Colbert (Box 50)
          - Galeries Lafayett (Box 50)
          - Grands Magazins Dufayel (Box 50)
          - Printemps (Box 50)
          - Samaritaine (Box 50)
          - Salon de l'Art Nouveau (Box 50)
        - Theaters (Box 50)
          - Opera [Slide boxes 299-300] (Box 50)
      - Pessac [Slide box 300] (Box 50)
      - Possy-sur-Seine [Slide boxes 300-301] (Box 50–51)
      - Pontoise [Slide box 301] (Box 51)
      - Ronchamps (Box 51)
        - Notre Dame du Haut (Box 51)
          - Exterior (Box 51)
          - Interior (Box 51)
      - Rouen [Slide box 302] (Box 51)
      - Royan (Box 51)
      - S. Cloud (Box 51)
      - S. Denis (Box 51)
      - S. Lo (Box 51)
      - Roquebrune (Box 51)
        - Cabin (Le Corbusier) (Box 51)
        - E.1027 House (Eileen Gray) (Box 51)
      - S. Quentin-en-Yvelines (Box 51)
      - S. Paul-de-Vence (Box 51)
      - Sceaux (Box 51)
      - Souillac (Box 51)
      - Strassbourg [Slide box 303] (Box 51)
      - Thiepval (Box 51)
      - Toulouse (Box 51)
      - Trouville (Box 51)
      - Vaucresson (Box 51)
      - Vence (Box 51)
      - Verdun (Box 51)
      - Versailles (Box 51)
      - Ville d'Avray (Box 51)
      - Villeurbanne (Box 51)
  - Germany (Box 51)
    - General (Box 51)
      - Highways [Slide boxes 303-304] (Box 51)
    - Architects [Slide box 304] (Box 51)
      - Bartning, Otto (Box 51)
      - Bayer, Herbert (Box 51)
      - Behrens, Peter (Box 51)
      - Deutschen Werkbundes (Box 51)
      - Finsterlin, Hermann (Box 51)
      - Gropius, Walter (Box 51)
      - Hablik, Wenzel (Box 51)
      - Hilbersceimer, Ludwig (Box 51)
      - Klenze, Leo von (Box 51)
      - Kreis, Wilhelm (Box 51)
      - Krier, Leon (Box 51)
        - Bagnano House (Box 51)
          - Bremen Project (Box 51)
          - London Project (Box 51)
          - Luxembourg Project [Slide box 305] (Box 51)
          - Monument with Faded Red Flag (Box 51)
          - Paris: La Villette Quarter (Box 51)
          - S. Quentin en Yvelines (Box 51)
      - Krier, Robert (Box 51)
      - Luckhardt, W. (Box 51)
      - Mendelsohn, Eric (Box 51)
      - Mies van der Rohe [Slide boxes 305-306] (Box 51)
      - Obrist, Hermann [Slide box 306] (Box 51)
      - Olbrich, Josef (Box 51)
      - Otto, Frei (Box 51)
      - Poelzig, Hans (Box 51)
      - Scharoun, Hans (Box 51)
      - Schinkel, K.F. (Box 51)
      - Speer, Albert (Box 51)
      - Taut, Bruno (Box 51)
      - Taut, Max (Box 51)
      - Tessenow, Heinrich (Box 51)
      - Unger, O.M. (Box 51)
    - Cities [Slide box 307] (Box 52)
      - Aachen (Box 52)
      - Alfeld an der Leine (Box 52)
      - Alt-Ruppen (Box 52)
      - Annaberg (Box 52)
      - Auschwitz (Box 52)
      - Bad Friedrichshall (Box 52)
      - Baden (Box 52)
      - Berlin (Box 52)
        - Churches (Box 52)
        - Exhibitions (Box 52)
        - Government Buildings (Box 52)
          - Chancellery [Slide boxes 307-308] (Box 52)
          - Main Guard House [Slide box 308] (Box 52)
        - Houses- Apartments (Box 52)
          - Hansaviertel (Box 52)
        - Houses- Residential (Box 52)
          - Villa Ende (Box 52)
          - Sommerfeld (Box 52)
        - Housing (Box 52)
          - Britz "Gehag" (Box 52)
          - Gartenstadt Staaken (Box 52)
          - Hellersdorf District (Box 52)
          - IBA Social Housing on Kochstrasse (Box 52)
          - Lutzowplatz [Slide box 309] (Box 52)
          - Schiesisches Tor Housing (Box 52)
          - Siemensstadt Housing (Box 52)
          - Trierer-Strasse (Box 52)
          - Wedding (Box 52)
          - Wohnstadt Carl Legien (Box 52)
        - Industrial Buildings (Box 52)
          - AEG Assembly Hall (Box 52)
          - AEG High Tension Works (Box 52)
          - AEG Small Motors (Box 52)
          - AEG Turbine Factory (Box 52)
        - Libraries (Box 52)
        - Museums (Box 52)
          - Altes Museum (Box 52)
          - Jewish Museum (Box 52)
          - New National Gallery [Slide box 310] (Box 52)
        - Office Buildings (Box 52)
        - Palaces (Box 52)
        - Parks (Box 52)
        - Schools (Box 52)
          - Architecture Academy (Box 52)
          - Charlottenburg Technical University (Box 52)
        - Squares (Box 52)
        - Stadiums (Box 52)
        - Stations (Box 52)
        - Stores (Box 52)
        - Theaters (Box 52)
          - Capitol (Box 52)
          - Grosses Schauspielhaus (Box 52)
          - Schauspielhaus [Slide box 311] (Box 52)
          - Philharmonics Hall (Box 52)
      - Bischofsheim (Box 52)
      - Bonn (Box 52)
      - Bremen (Box 52)
      - Breslau (Box 52)
      - Chemnitz (Box 52)
      - Cleve (Box 52)
      - Coesfeld (Box 52)
      - Cologne (Box 52)
        - Werkbund Exhibition 1914 (Box 52)
        - Werkbund Exhibition "Fabrik" (Box 52)
        - Werkbund Exhibition "Glass House" (Box 52)
      - Crossinsee (Box 52)
      - Dachau (Box 52)
      - Dahlewitz (Box 52)
      - Darmstadt (Box 52)
        - Artists' Colony [Slide boxes 311-312] (Box 52)
          - Artists' Colony Houses [Slide box 312] (Box 52)
        - Wedding Tower and Exhibition Hall (Box 52)
      - Dekstern (Box 52)
      - Dessau (Box 52)
        - Bauhaus (Box 52)
      - Dresden [Slide boxes 312-313] (Box 52–53)
      - Dusseldorf [Slide box 313] (Box 53)
      - Eller (Box 53)
      - Erfurt (Box 53)
      - Essen (Box 53)
      - Frankfurt (Box 53)
        - Crafts Museum (Box 53)
        - I.G. Farben Fabrik (Box 53)
        - Synagogues (Box 53)
      - Guben (Box 53)
      - Hagen (Box 53)
        - Cuno House (Box 53)
        - Folkwang Museum (Box 53)
        - Hohenhof (Box 53)
      - Hamburg (Box 53)
        - Chilehaus (Box 53)
      - Hanover (Box 53)
      - Heidelberg [Slide box 314] (Box 53)
      - Hellerau (Box 53)
      - Hochst-am-Main (Box 53)
      - Hohenschwangau (Box 53)
      - Jena (Box 53)
      - Karinhall (Prussia) (Box 53)
      - Karlsruhe (Box 53)
      - Kassel (Box 53)
      - Kelheim (Box 53)
      - Krefeld (Box 53)
      - Leipzig (Box 53)
      - Linderhof (Box 53)
      - Luban (Box 53)
      - Lubeck (Box 53)
      - Luckenwalde (Box 53)
      - Magdeburg (Box 53)
      - Merseburg (Box 53)
      - Monchengladbach (Box 53)
      - Munich (Box 53)
        - Churches (Box 53)
        - Expositions (Box 53)
        - Gates (Box 53)
        - Government Buildings (Box 53)
        - Housing (Box 53)
        - Libraries (Box 53)
        - Monuments [Slide box 315] (Box 53)
        - Museums (Box 53)
          - Glyptothek (Box 53)
          - House of German Art (Box 53)
        - Schools (Box 53)
          - Studio Elvira (Box 53)
        - Squares (Box 53)
        - Theaters (Box 53)
      - Neubabelsberg (Box 53)
      - Neu-Ulm (Box 53)
      - Neuschwanstein (Box 53)
      - Neuss (Box 53)
      - Nuremberg (Box 53)
      - Ordensburg (Box 53)
      - Posen (Box 53)
      - Potsdam [Slide box 316] (Box 53)
        - Einstein Tower (Box 53)
        - Churches (Box 53)
        - Houses (Box 53)
        - Palaces (Box 53)
          - Charlottenhof (Box 53)
      - Regensburg (Box 53)
      - Rummelsberg (Box 53)
      - Schoneberg (Box 53)
      - Stahnsdorf (Box 53)
      - Stettin (Box 53)
      - Stuttgart (Box 53)
        - Housing (Box 53)
          - Weissenhof (Box 53)
            - Houses by Gropius (Box 53)
            - Houses by Le Corbusier (Box 53)
            - Houses by Mies van der Rohe [Slide box 317] (Box 53)
        - Museums (Box 53)
        - Stores (Box 53)
      - Tannenburg (Box 53)
      - Ulm (Box 53)
      - Weil-am-Rhine [Slide boxes 317-318] (Box 53)
        - Parks [Slide box 318] (Box 53)
      - Weimar (Box 53)
        - Art School (Box 53)
        - Monument to the Dead (Box 53)
      - Wiesbaden (Box 53)
      - Worpswede (Box 53)
      - Wurzburg (Box 53)
  - Greece (Box 53)
    - Athens (Box 53)
    - Rhodes (Box 53)
  - Holland (Box 53)
    - Architects (Box 53)
      - Bazel, K.P.C. de (Box 53)